To silence, stitch my ribs with smoke, build altars out of every word I never spoke.
My mercy was the womb that never healed, and I keep reopening.
Once against the council of my bones
Watched you slip into the black
But um, you know what?
Promise you will be better than ever watch this look at this what I got actually is it ready yet? I can't show you
Well, I can show you hold on
Hold on a second
I can show you something look what I got
for you. Hold on a minute. Oh, it's okay guys. You know what's okay because you know why there's
a million things it could be. It could be like I have porn, um, porn bombs in several past streams
And then, you know, they have AI, they have these AI, AI bots going through
There's a lot of pressure being monetized on YouTube. There's actually like, you know, I was probably doing better with the super chats and
You know, the memberships are pretty much dried up and I didn't like some of the direction it was going
So, you know what? Maybe it's a fresh start. Maybe it's the blessing in disguise, you know
Have you ever heard of blessing in disguises? I have I believe in it. I believe everything happens for a reason
Whether whatever happens whether whatever happens, you know what?
I'm still here
I'm still fucking here
You know what now it's gonna be better than ever now I can like fucking relax a little bit now
I can be like, okay, I'll just for fun. I'll do this for fun. Yeah, blessing in disguise. Okay. Yeah, it really is
Uh, post the link rookie. Oh, King Carl. No, no, no. I'm going to show you something else. I'm showing something else right now. Well, it's like that.
Um,
Let's see.
I'm not, I'm no rookie. I'm a veteran. I'm a veteran of this bullshit.
Um, okay. Okay. Well, I guess I have to do this way.
Do this.
Okay, I can close that close that close that close that up
Almost closed everything, okay
Okay, I want to show you something look what I got
Look what I got
Guys, isn't it like also really good time. It's like perfect timing actually based on like what I was just doing
With this site, so have a look have a look, okay?
So I'm going to share my screen, okay, and I guess I'll share the entire screen, okay.
Do we see?
You see what's going on here?
Do you see it?
I don't know if you can see it, okay, but I'm sharing the screen, okay.
We have the Cult of Psyche website, I'm trying to, yeah, I did change the spelling, so it
needs to reflect that shortly.
Oh, yeah, see, it already has it there.
Let's see, welcome to the cult of Psycheosanctum, where wisdom wears a grin and revelation runs
on Wi-Fi.
This isn't just a website, it's a living broadcast, half oracle, half algorithm, where
streamers become seers and creators find communion in the current.
Here consciousness is both the medium and the message.
We don't follow trends, we divine them, we don't chase content, we channel it.
Step inside the signal, awaken the stream with them, okay?
have a membership going through here now.
Daily affirmation to speak is to shape reality.
Every sentence, the spell disguises sound, okay?
You can also receive another if you want.
Three pillars of consciousness, creation, and community.
We have the three C's, right?
We have offering oracle speaks.
We have voices from the call.
We have, you know, you can join the call.
And also look.
The live stream my on look. I'm on my website
It's a no matter and also you can set it up to receive
Yeah
I have it set up so you can receive notifications when the show's on and stuff. Okay, so and I still got this
You know, and then I'll start another backup channel here. Okay, something happens in this one
I'll just like play the musical chairs a background stuff, you know
I'm not gonna not try to be monetized and so it's basically like just like, you know, I
Mean I am monetized. I'll be monetized through several other things not YouTube related. You know, I mean, it's like well, maybe some but
Not through the partner program. Maybe someday they'll they'll have me back
They are doing some grace periods for some people, but I think I would need to wait a little while
so
So 2020 you're the person that is all is all mean to me and stuff
King Carl, you don't dream on psyche
I'm not post-amening for you you go to hell King Carl
Why would you say why would you why would you come here? Why King Carl got blocked? Why?
He doesn't he doesn't you don't run shit. You don't run shit Carl
Whatever
And I know like you just trying to hoodwink Alexandra, and I know you know you're all like lying about oh
I mean, you know, oh, yeah, I just want to yeah, I know I know I don't trust you
You'd have told me all about you and I do trust what she said about you
You know
Go cast some black magic on some other ex viewers or something. Okay?
Mimi watch out. He's gonna he's gonna he's gonna use black magic on you. It's what he does to his girlfriends
Okay
It's not good
Not good at all
Anyway
And now I can freely talk though. Oh my gosh, I can I can really share so many things. I wanted to share too
Oh my gosh, I have so many good things to share with you guys
So many good things to share with you guys. Let me look hook it off. They'll kick it off with like a fun
Fun fun song
And this might take a chance.
This channel down tonight, you know,
but guys, it was quite a run wasn't it?
No, it'll be fine.
Playing that song.
Oh, she was laughing. Oh, well, I didn't laugh when she lost her channel. It happened to her.
Same exact thing, except that she was a monetize. But you know what? Why is she laughing? I'm right
here on YouTube. 17 people in my chat. Like, it does probably better than my usual would be
getting. Hey, Bubbles. Hey, everybody. I'm fine. I'm fine. We are all, it's just another freaking
I love you guys. She said it's my karma. Well, I'll tell her her karma. Her karma is to have her
last name put out and suspicion about her and Aaron Carter and her ex-husband. That's her karma.
Okay, anyway, enough about...
What's her name?
Enough about her. I'm about to ban her name in my chat.
I sold myself shut. My weakness is that I can't do much and my scars remind me that the past is real.
I can't my heart open just to feel.
Don't get me down, I just want to be alone.
Cause the gentle all your pain
In a cave you think she'll steal
You're making me insane
Like I'm insane
Damn I'm out of my mind
I see so much sex now
I can't no higher, so offer to I am, compassion's in my nature.
You just go-
myself sure my weakness says that I care too much the skies alignment this is real
I tear my heart open just to feel I tear my heart open
self sure my weakness says that I care too much the stars
Remind us, the past is real. I tear my heart open just to fail.
That was a good song. How can you become a psyche member?
Um, well, if you'd like to be on the list, I mean, I'm remaking the membership right
now.
Yeah, you don't have to show me your asshole.
I think you just have to send five bucks and sign up on my, um, on the website, but it's
still like in, um, it's still in process.
I do not accept any asshole photos, um, guys, do not send me a photo of your asshole.
Can't even think of anybody's I want to see I can't even think of one person. I
Don't want to see anybody's I mean, it's like
Even like J-Duck I was like, oh, I don't want it. I didn't want to see that W2 that's like too much. It's like too intimate
That makes sense guys
Okay
But let me just I'm just gonna do a little stuff
Yeah, but this is gonna be a lot more fun for me though, it's gonna be a lot more fun
It's like it's I mean everything's worth it. It's it's gonna be fucking. It's like we just what I needed
I needed the new start. I need a new start and
You could tell I already was like, you know, I knew this would happen
I was just like I just felt it. It's felt it even this morning. I was like, this is the day is this the day
I'm gonna lose the chance. I just knew it. It's just like I
Knew it, but you know what?
I'm absolutely fine.
It's gonna be better.
Guys, you can use the hard R.
Come on, you can use the hard ER.
You can come talk about whatever political crap
you wanna talk about.
Okay.
Okay, I'm I'm gonna have some three
three levels of membership. So 499 will be the initiate
These are all gonna be available through the website when I have it ready. It'll be very shortly
Okay, okay
Okay, the 49 okay
a
Actually a 999 and a 1999. Okay. A 999.
And, and, okay. What will the 1999 entail? That'll entail
a 30 minutes a month private phone phone conversation for whatever you want to do.
Okay, but I'm working on it
Okay, but I know I'm gonna get some shit, too. I mean people are gonna be oh my god
Look, I told you how you do you're gonna fail blah blah blah blah
guys fail
Just another brick and though it's a little step
Little step, you know, at least the Jordana told me once she's like it doesn't even matter if you're monetized or not
she's like it because
You can set up your own payment system, so I mean she's she's monetized, but she doesn't use her super chat or her
memberships she just
or even, I don't even think she puts ads on her videos, right?
It's like she just didn't even use them in monetization.
So there's other ways.
I mean, it's like, so people will try to make me think,
oh, you know, this is like some kind of failure.
This is actually not a failure.
This is actually like a really good thing.
Cause also I was going to be more focused on my website,
which is now we'll have the, you know,
the cult of psyche TV there.
And so it'll have the discord integrated into it.
I'm having a really, really cool site.
been developing it for over a month,
that we're working really hard on it.
But guys, yeah,
if you guys wanna like start out tonight,
it's a little like, you know,
you know,
helping me out a little bit,
I would appreciate it because,
you know, it's not fun.
With this prospect and you know
Oliver, you know, I don't know. I don't know it. Yeah, so I and I will set up my power chat
I'll play music and stuff on the show, you know, you can have music on play fucking full songs now and
You can have the song say fuck you psyche you can like play your own AI songs
I will have the power chat set up. Okay, I'm gonna have to
look into fixing it with my
With my integration. I don't know. I still got bills to pay and everything. I mean, it's like it's just it's inconvenient
It's a little bit inconvenient. It's a little bit like wow like that's the rug pulled under me
But you know it could happen anytime to anybody it's happened to at least I'm actually a Emma Levi-10
Actually, she had something similar, but she was on a tick tock
She had 23,000 tick tock subscribers and she was doing well on tick tock and then
All of a sudden it's gone. You know what I can do? Now I can go on TikTok.
Now I can go do concentrate more and doing that more. I can have my shorter shows here.
I'll do more of the format I wanted. It's gonna be like just the show I wanted now
because I couldn't really like do everything when I wanted it when it was monetized.
So I didn't notice after I got monetized. I was like, okay, well, I don't know, right?
It's like you have to follow these dumb rules and it's like so now
whether or not I follow these dumb rules or not, I'm gonna be able to
Continue to maintain my my channels. Okay, I'm not scared. I'm not not worried. I'm not sad
I'm not even disappointed. I'm actually excited
You know, I'm actually excited
Okay, we have the membership page working now, um, let me see if I can
Okay
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, well, whatever.
Okay, so is everyone in here gonna just gonna try to pick on me and like say, oh you suck and like, you know
Everyone's right about you. That's okay. I don't care
At the end of the day at the end of the day at the end of the day like like I've already done at the end of the day
Hey, you know what?
Hey, there's always a rumble with Chris K. I can always go to rumble with Chris K, right?
Yeah, Tony
Over a mobile at Chris K doing Chattabate and rumble, okay?
I'm sorry. That was bad in New York. It was worse in New York accent than his. I need some water.
Oh, no talking about Emma. Go away. That's with my tongue. That thing's wrong with my tongue.
The thing that looks wrong with it.
Something wrong with it, guys. It looks pink. Samantha, my, you know, unfortunately my channel
is deleted by YouTube, but, you know, I still got this one. I still got pretty, well, not very active.
Leave but you know, it's just fine. I'll bet I already it was basically like
You know not going well, I'll just say it wasn't going well
I mean it was going well with the views and stuff. It was just not going well with
Me be happy. So I'm not I was I was not very happy. I was not happy with how things are going
I was not it's all numb. I'm fine. I don't need some water. I just need some weed
So
How am I going to beg for fish talk I can beg for fish money talk of money here
You see I'm still on YouTube. Do you see hello? Hello? I'm here on YouTube. I even have the same channel name practically
Now it's starts with a K like because I'm on kick too, right?
so I can beg for fish taco money here, but I
Really need to I know I never beg for fish taco money in my life
Actually, I got a donation one time for Dubai fish talkers of the pier, and then I didn't have data on my phone
So I did beg for some money for data
Which turned out I didn't even need because I was able to pay with PayPal and stuff. But anyway
That's besides the point, you know, whatever lore you want to guys want to make up and shit like that
I'm just gonna be myself now. It's like now. It's like I don't have to like worry about oh
I have to be one of the e-bike stays cursed until I stop
bringing her up and start letting,
are you KZ Fred Aleister?
Cause you're so interested in Emma and KZ.
I know, why does it bother any,
I don't know why it bothers them Jamie,
but they're just going to say stuff
cause they're trolls and they're like sad trolls.
And it's like, but you know what?
Yeah, what does it matter to them?
I'm going to start remodding some people now though too.
And of course, you know, I'm going to be very more,
much more careful how I mod people.
From now on, it's like, I think I'm,
I think I'm going to be like modding.
Um, people that are initiates, like, um, you know, basically, um, exclusively, because
I do have to, like, you know, step up my monetization game and, you know, no, uh, no
You can go ahead and become a member.
Let me just make sure I can verify that I own this site in a second, I'll be right back.
You're safe to mod. Thank you in advance. We'll go ahead.
You need some wrench crack. We'll go ahead and buy an initiatory membership.
I'm going to get my, you know, you can always, my cash up fortunately is still working fine.
send that even if it doesn't because I'm still working on integration with PayPal for it.
So if you send it, I'll make sure to award you membership. Okay.
So thank you guys
Yeah, so if you would you know, I really would appreciate
You know now that we've gotten to this point when I say eventually it's like you know
Imagine if it was like I got to this point when I was like it thought it was like huge, right? I thought it was big, right?
Basically my channel. I thought my channel wasn't dying, but it was just like it's just like the people
The crowd was like just like a hostile crowd. I was uncomfortable. I was like, you know, didn't like
I just have to step out in front of it.
So basically, yeah, it's all going to work out.
It's all going to be good.
Let me just make sure I have a certain thing.
I need to check one more thing.
Just give me a minute.
I'm going to play a video.
I'll be back.
Switching the stove
in the dark, praise in the bloom, the night is the canvas, where visions move and
fall.
Oh, to fight me, Bo is a, that's King Carl.
And beat as a witch too.
Yeah, we all know that.
Hey, DJ Electra, did you get my message?
My channel's down, I've got taken down.
So we're here, we're here at this one.
It's gone.
Not Carl, sure you're not.
Fight me, Bo, are you either Carl or KZ or something?
I mean, it's one of those lames.
What am I gonna do?
What am I gonna do
cosmic law steaming our veins salt in our eyes
and tied to our souls now we baptize
for the world and our buddha creed at the altar of hunger
Sigh me please
a page and a follow start chatting the shelves start to glow
ghosts draw symbols in the undertow
goddess calls click time with faith the thing that is whispers the pot can't
People red and raw
Snapping our claws at the cosmic law
play like an actual real song.
So it's gonna be kind of a downer.
Okay, so I'll play this song.
This is one of my favorite songs.
And this woman named Joni, you know Joni in my chat,
she turned me back on to the song.
And so I hope you like the song.
This is for you guys.
In case you didn't know.
Where did it lose you?
Where are you?
Oh, here.
Oh, there you are.
I'll fix Nightbot, I'll fix Nightbot.
They say you have to stay in use for free economic sake.
Well, I don't really because it's like what I wasn't making who to like, who donated anyway, hardly anybody just like, you know, good friends, like, you know,
Electra and, you know, ghosts and, uh, and people that had memberships and some people, some people that have donated along the way. I appreciate, um, but.
have to worry about. I'm free. I'm a free guy. Fortunately, unfortunately, unfortunately,
or fortunately, unfortunately, I am free. That's a good thing and a bad thing. Okay,
anyway, figure out later. I'll figure out later. Here, enjoy the song. This is my song
I wish I had been
I must leave me
Thank you
Listen to those things to you
And so I have to say before I go
Smashing pumpkin James e-ha a little bit, didn't he? Yeah, he kind of did
Mmm
Okay, guys, I guess rumble premium is calling out for me rumble premium guys anyone rumble premium anyone
Yeah, I'm a little bit
one second, four, okay. Hold on a second. I'm trying to, I'm trying to, oops, stop sharing.
I'm trying to do something. Oh shit. Okay. Okay. There we go. Yeah. Reminds me to destroy
rebuild, right? So Phoenix coming from the egg. The only thing is I'm just like worried
about a couple of things, but everything will work out. Everything will work out. Let me
just say, I just need to get an instruction to do something real quick. Okay.
Excuse me, I know I'm a little bit flustered right now a little bit flustered, but I'm not like, you know
It's kind of like whoa, what's just happened like it's gonna like whoa, but it's kind of like I trust
Hey, Apollo
Hey, can you guys let panel verse no panel verse VODs know that this is the new channel?
I'm also gonna be I'm on streaming on kick. So guys
My kick is this this is like the name on kick
For now my I'm probably gonna change it as soon as I can to like cult of psyche, right?
But it that's it right now
So make sure you subscribe to that and then on my website, which I'm about to get up in the cash app. Yeah
No, oh damn. So 21 might call you are Tony first of all, but 21. Why would why would I be here? Why would I be here?
But why would I be here? And he didn't win because actually I was like pretty much
Wanting to like fucking do away with that, you know, like the monetization was better on cash up anyway
I don't like the the fact that it's like, oh my god. If this is said is this is said
It's okay, you know, YouTube is mom, you know, at least a Jordan like I just said is monetized on YouTube
But does she use super chats?
Does she use membership?
Does she have ads?
No, she has PowerChat.
So now I'll be able to put PowerChat in
and it'll be even the same thing.
Actually, I'll get the money faster
and I share less with YouTube.
So it's even better.
And 100% of your donations will go to me.
Oh, who care?
I don't care who the fuck it is.
I think they got fired for my job.
Actually, it wasn't my job
because YouTube was a partnership.
And so it's just basically like, you know,
partnership dissolved,
but I can still, I'm still using the platform.
But yeah.
Oh yeah, but one thing I'm going to be doing is like really like having people I want in the chat and people that I don't want in the chat are going to be sacrificed to Matangi, okay?
So just a heads up.
Also, um, YouTube is doing second chances, um, with people, but it's like, it takes a
little, you know, it'll take probably a few months before they offer that to me if they
do.
So, we'll see what happens.
We'll see what happens.
Okay.
Let me just have a look.
Yeah.
So, I'm going to switch channel.
This is not good anymore.
Okay.
Switch that out.
Okay, I'm in. I'm in. Okay. Okay, I'm in. Okay. I know I can go into YouTube. I can
still do all the same things I can basically do. I have all the features with streaming
Okay, there we go, cult of psyche and
okay, ban, oh yeah, well if it, but my call, if it was, I am, and you're banned by the way,
so that's something, yeah, if I did, if I like had a monetized channel, I might worry about that,
but like what are they gonna do? They take away my, they already took away my channel,
so the worst, they've done the worst, you know, it's like, they take away this channel.
So another one I have another I've another if you lined up
Don't think I hit 50 subscribers pretty quickly
Plus I have my website now going and it's gonna be able to stream from there
So it's even better like because I didn't even think about oh
I can have my like whole website as my own kind of network my own station and stuff
And I can just and I just you know use kind of twitch is the framework of it
Yeah
Well, and I'm live right now
Okay, well, go ahead. Yeah
Yeah, I wasn't um, yeah, I wasn't banned. I was just the channel was deleted. It wasn't it's not a ban of agent
It's not like because if it's like if they say, oh, well, well, we're waiting for a decision on one channel
Don't stream on another channel
That's kind of what I was doing like several months ago when I was like on here when I had the other channel suspended
That was that but
Um, yeah, it's not bannabating, but he, anyway, the little person that banned this ban here right now is Mike Hall, and he's not funny. And he's a really terrible comedian.
And he can go fuck a duck.
Okay.
I'm probably just gonna leave the mods on a smaller scale
unless you're like a like a member of the cult I can initiate okay okay okay anyway um so let's see
now I need to
Do one more thing real quick, and then I should have the website up and
Jiffy
It's already working pretty well. It got the chat up there. You got the twitch chat there
So no matter what happens, I'll be fine
Yeah, I'm not worried about any threats anymore. I mean, I really wasn't I mean, it's like, you know
But I knew I was like, wow, it's like really hard to maintain monetization if you're being attacked and it's like, you know
Just constantly people are just trying to fuck with you. It's oh, it's okay. It's like it's better
It's just like less stress now. I can say the n-word, but I don't say the n-word
But I could I could say it if I said it, but I don't say it and I don't want anyone else to say it
but you can say it but just don't say it and
I don't know. I just don't like it
Anyway, it's just not a word I use. I don't even need I don't even use the soft
soft a oh
Yeah, and by the way, you can go check out
Somebody named Benjamin Kowalski. His mom is on
only fans for eight dollars and
And his dad we are in contact with as well. So yeah, Benjamin Kowalski everybody
Hey, how about Seckie always wins Ben? Sorry
Oh, he's he got mad at that one. He got mad at that one. Oh, I hit a little close to home
Old Tony Kowalski
Kowalski
What are you saying he says shekels he said shekels
Oh, he said Jew. He's called me a fake Jew. You're Jewish, Tony. It's okay. It's okay. I don't need that. I don't need YouTube show.
He said Shekels. Well, it was Shekels. It was just like, you know, this little spirit chain. It was just a little, it was basically for fun.
Yeah. Tony, yeah, we, I'm in contact with your father and your mother on OnlyFans, okay? $8 OnlyFans. I'm going to be posting your link very shortly.
It's okay. I wouldn't mind if your mom was only fancy.
Do I care about TOS Tony? Do I even fucking care? Stop texting me. You're harassing me.
This is against the law what you're doing. Oh, please. You don't even know who you're talking about.
You don't even know who you're talking about.
don't make me subscribe to your mom's page and share it with everybody
and i will say the n word i'll call you the n word okay because that's what you are
you call me a fake jew i never claimed that was jewish okay tony okay stop harassing me
what i said that you're jewish i didn't say that i'm jewish okay um and i love jewish people
You're the one ex you're the one Jew. I don't like it. Maybe I'm that uh
That Harvey Weinstein and a Jeffrey Epstein character, but everybody else is great. Um, okay, let me see
Yeah, I think what most saw it was a little bit too hot on the page Tony, I don't need a job. Please Tony Tony
I'm sitting pretty okay
I'm sitting pretty
Do I look like I'm concerned one bit you thought you were gonna destroy me didn't you didn't you think I was gonna be destroyed
I'm not a government leech and plus the government's not even paying out right now, so I'd be really concerned, but yeah
No, I don't get government assistance and so
Not concerned at all
And I'm 44
Oh, you didn't take shit Tony if you took it if you took it
Oh, you took you took it. I mean you take all the negativity all the bad karma all the all the sickness sadness everything negative about it
Just take it. It's all yours. Take it. I send it all to you and
Everybody I'm gonna I'm gonna show this motherfucker's picture. I'm gonna show this movie
I'm gonna show this motherfucker's picture. He called he's calling me Cyrax right now
I'm gonna show this motherfucker's picture right now on a discord, okay?
I'm gonna show it on discord and this will stay up forever on kick. Okay?
Oh my god, now he's saying I tried to R-word him.
I'm gonna show his picture.
Okay guys, do you wanna see this monster?
Wanna see him?
Wanna see how he looks like?
Oh yeah, you can see him.
Tony is Benjamin Kowalski.
Yeah, I'll show this picture.
Yeah, I'm not afraid anymore.
I'm not worried about anything.
Let me see.
I'll put up a video, actually.
I have a video, I have a whole video of him.
And he's trying to preen for the camera.
Here you go.
I don't care if you report it. I don't care. I don't care Tony. I don't care. Oh
My gosh, I might have cared if I had my account, but I don't know I don't have it
So what do I care? What do I care? What the fuck do I care Tony Tony?
You're you're the Tony baloney. You're Tony baloney. Okay. Anyway, let's me let me find I need to get this this video real quick
Where's this video? Oh here it is. Okay?
Oh my god. Oh, he's he's horrendous. He's just horrendous. Okay, where are you? Where are you?
Oh my god, do you hear that? Guys, you hear that? He's just going crazy. I'm going to doon-to-doon.
Just going crazy. Uh-oh. I'm gonna exit my mod chat. Okay, one second. He's just going nuts.
I'm about to show it. I'm about to embarrass you, Tony Bologna. I'm about to embarrass you.
Everyone's going to see what you look like. Everyone's going to see what you look like.
Everybody's going to see what you look like.
Okay. Oh my gosh, I'm seeing many mansons. Old text. Oh, those are the days.
I don't see it there anymore. Do you want to take it down? Hold on. Main text chat. Is it this one?
Oh, I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Guys, do you want to see this monster? Do you want to see this monster?
Here. Okay, I'm okay. This guy's calling me the new Cyrax. When I see this guy, this guy is calling me the new Cyrax.
Okay, look at this guy. Oh my god. Look at this. This is gonna be scary guys. Guys, this is scary.
This is the guy calling me the new Cyrax, okay?
This is the guy right here.
Look at this monster look at this monster guys exposed
Now leave beat alone. Oh, you don't seem a chat you probably you blocked him probably which which I should do
No, no, no, he's not no. He's not in chat. He's take he's texting me on my phone
Beedah didn't do anything of the sort and be the has no power to do that
Neither does he you don't you don't person that does is me and I think I know what I did it was because I've
Not careful
You'll take turns over to you now. Oh good luck, Tony. Tony. Do you think I care? This is not a monetized channel
I can I can start a new channel
No, probably Benjamin Kowalski
No problem Benjamin Kowalski. Benjamin Kowalski. This is the guy guys. This is allied master computer Tony
Benjamin Kowalski. This is him right there. This is him. This is the monster
Look at this guy
Hold on. Look at this. Look at this guy
Look at him
horrific
He looks like he looks like a really holy woman
Oh, can you share that with me, Electra? I want the... I think that is him, though.
It's worse than this? Well, let's see it. Who is this person? Oh my gosh. What does it say in my Discord? Hold on a second. It says...
Um, on my Discord, it says...
To that allied and then no one says anything. I don't know if it's okay. I don't know. Maybe it's just somebody's picture
No, maybe oh my gosh. I'm so sorry if that was just
Adhesive if that was just your actual picture
Then I apologize, okay
If you're just trying to share your photo and I always called you weird and everything I don't know
Someone's what would you what do you say?
See if take over let me see where's the freak out. I don't I don't I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what's going on in the chat
Okay, I need to hook up my um
My new website real quick. So just give me one minute. I'm gonna put on a song up and I'll be right back. Oh, excuse me. I love you guys
Thanks for hanging out with me
Take that scary thing off the stage
It was a spark, not a throne
All I ever needed was a life to call my own
All I ever dreamed was someone new here
The voice in the dark say, you belong here
All I ever wanted was truth in the static
A little bit of real in the world so dramatic
Kept my calm while the crowd threw stones
your gift they laughed when I fell but I danced in the dirt every scar I got
just rewrote my worth all I ever wanted was to free my fear to turn my pain to
something clear now I bleed are not worried I make heaven from the mess they
make we are paniverse profits wild and weird streaming our truth for the world
to hear not broken just beautifully bent a choir of chaos that heaven said
Hey, BlackRG.
RG, I've had open panels almost the whole time and it's like I really like what
Yeah, I really want that many open panels. No, I don't I don't want to see that many open panels because
They're annoying. They're just fucking annoying bunch of I mean, I think I like some people but most of the people I just like
No, I could do without I come up here, right?
I'm sorry if you fall into the, no, no, no.
I love all you guys.
Yeah.
Yeah, KZ is a total panel barnacle.
Guys, can you help me out though?
Since I, since, you know, officially, you know,
I have one less paycheck coming in a month.
If you could help me out, if you could purchase reading,
if you could purchase an astrological report,
and then the membership will be available on the website
as soon as I get this forwarded
and it will just take a few minutes, but.
We shall see okay
But guys, I just I'm in such a better memory
I was like I'm in such a better mood than I was yesterday and yesterday
I still have my sight today. I don't and I'm in a better mood. Just go figure. Isn't that weird?
Because I because I was ready for I was ready for that's another good song
Isn't it a good song? Hold on. Let's play that one.
I am a woman.
Oh, good gracious, good gracious. Good golly, Miss Molly.
Some boys are trying too hard, you can try it all though
There's an excess for the efforts of your man though
And nothing's left of it, I just need to run and run
But nothing's left of it, I just need to run and run
You should see the things we're doing, baby
We're in the middle of the night in my dreams
I don't compare when you're slow, you're taking my time
Are you ready for it?
I can go by myself, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island, I'll go to an island,
Now, I, I, I see where this is gonna go
And you let them know
I can feel it like they know
No one has to know
In the middle of the night
In my dreams
You should see the things we do
Baby, ooh
In the middle